utsavsarees.in 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy - Utsavfashion.com

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.utsavfashion.com/ (the “Site”).

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. We may also collect information about you through social media sites you use to access our Site depending the permissions you have given for access to your information.  
Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

**COOKIES & OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES THAT WE USE:**

We and our service providers use cookies, beacons & embedded scripts in connection with the Sites.

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
  * An “Embedded script” is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or device from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

The above technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the Sites, services and products, tracking users’ movements around the Sites and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.  
We use cookies to remember users’ settings, market products and services to users, and for authentication purposes.

**Third-Party Advertising Services:** We partner with third parties that may use technologies such as cookies (and local stored objects as described above) to gather information about your activities on the Sites and elsewhere on the Internet in order to provide you with relevant advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. This type of advertising is sometimes called interest-based advertising. No personally-identifiable information is collected or used in this process.

**Third-Party Analytics:** We may also use service providers, such as Google Analytics, that may use cookies or other technologies to collect information about your online activities across this and other sites over time for non-advertising purposes such as those described above. To learn more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data and the choices Google may offer to control these activities, you may visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/.

**Google Analytics:** To help facilitate the delivery of relevant content, we use Google Analytics and have implemented the following Google Advertising Features: Remarketing, Impression Reporting, and Demographics and Interest Reporting. We use Google Analytics cookies and other Google advertising cookies. You can opt out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use by indicating your preference using the interest-based opt-out link [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/). Google also provides a complete privacy policy, and instructions on opting out of Google Analytics [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Note that Google’s opt-out mechanism is specific to Google activities and does not affect the activities of other ad networks or analytics providers that we may use.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (we do not store your credit card information), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use personal information to:

  * We may also use your Personal Information to improve and personalize your experience with us, and, with your consent where necessary, send you information about us and keep you informed of our other products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * Communicate with you & send marketing mailers to which you have consented ;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud;
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
  * We use passively collected information to monitor and maintain the performance of our Sites, analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our services, validate users and ensure their technological compatibility with users, and optimise our marketing efforts.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this Privacy Policy or otherwise with your permission. We reserve the right to transfer data, including aggregate and de-identified data derived from Personal Information, for lawful purposes in our discretion.

  * We may share Personal Information with affiliated businesses.
  * Service Providers. We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies ("Service Providers") to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, and hosting services. When we employ a Service Provider to perform a function of this nature, we provide it with the information that it needs to perform its specific function, which may include Personal Information and other information that you provide to us via a Site. These companies are authorised to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * Third Parties for Marketing and Other Purposes. With your prior consent, we may share with selected third party partners for our marketing purposes.
  * Legal Requirements.We may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
  * Business Transfers. As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, total or partial sale of assets in bankruptcy or similar event, Personal Information may be part of the transferred assets, but this will be conducted in compliance with Indian law
  * Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to you from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our Sites. When you interact with content from our partners displayed on our Site, please be aware that you are providing your Personal Information to these third parties and it will be governed by their respective privacy policies.

**OUR OPT-OUT POLICY**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  
For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

  * FACEBOOK - <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>
  * GOOGLE - <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>
  * BING - <https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads>

Additionally, If you wish to not have this information collected and used for interest-based advertising, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/?pid=truste01&aid=preference_manager01&type=public) for partners that participate in the TRUSTe opt-out tool (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). If you wish to opt-out from this type of advertising for companies that participate in the Network Advertising Initiative, please [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/). If you wish to opt-out from this type of advertising for companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), you can do so [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/). Please note that this does not opt you out of being served ads.

**Email Marketing:** To stop receiving newsletters or marketing communications from us or to opt out of having your email address shared with third parties, please use the “unsubscribe” mechanism provided in the communication (such as the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the marketing email) or send an e-mail to info@utsavfashion.com along with the information necessary for us to process your request.

**Service-Related Announcements:** We will also send you service-related email announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not promotional in nature.

**DO NOT TRACK**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.  
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**DATA RETENTION**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**MINORS**

Visitors under 13 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their Personal Information at any Site. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not submit any information to us. In the event that we learn that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such personal information. Visitors older than the age of 13, but younger than their country’s legal age of majority are permitted to use and/or submit their Personal Information only with parental supervision.

**MISCELLANEOUS**

  * **Access to Personally Identifiable Information:** If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or delete it by emailing our Customer Support here(https://help.utsavfashion.com/support/home). We will respond to your request to access within 24 to 48 hours. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
  * **Links to Other Sites:** Our website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Utsav. Please be aware that we, Utsav, is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.
  * **Public Forums:** Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, email us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
  * **Customer Testimonials and Reviews:** We post customer testimonials and reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. When a customer chooses to post a review of a product, we ask for a nickname and location. If you would like to request to have your testimonial or review removed from our site you may email us.
  * **Social Media Widgets.** Our Sites may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets such as the share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Sites. These features may collect your IP address, which pages you are visiting on our Sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

**CHANGES**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**CONTACT US**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by [e-mail](https://help.utsavfashion.com/support/tickets/new) or by mail using the details provided below:  
12th Floor, DN 51, Merlin Infinite, Salt Lake City, Kolkata, WB, 700091, India
